talentsprint.com 2019-08-06

# Deep Tech Expertise for Professionals and Graduates - TalentSprint

This Privacy Policy (“ **Policy** ”) provides information about how TalentSprint Private Limited, a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 having its registered office at PSR Prime Towers, Suite No. G02, 101 & 102 Sy No 126 (P), beside DLF Cyber City, Gachibowli, Hyderabad, Rangareddy, TG- 560032 (the “ **Website Provider** ”) collects, uses, stores, archives and transfers information/data (used interchangeably hereafter) from you, through your use of the website www.talentsprint.com (“ **Website** ”)

### Scope

This Policy covers only data collected through the Website and not any other data collection or processing, including, without limitation, data collection practices of other mobile applications or web pages that are linked to the Website or data that is collected offline or through web sites, products, or services offered or belonging to third parties. Occasionally, reference would be made to this Policy in notices and consent requests related to specific surveys, ratings or other modalities present in the Website.

### Types of Data and Collection Methods

The following instances are when data might be collected by the Website Provider; when you (i) request information; (ii)apply to use or participate in or subscribe to any service offered through the Website; (iii) submit any content in the Website; (iv) register as a user; or (vi) otherwise actively send data through/using the Website. The Website Provider will collect, use, store and archive information about you in the following general categories:

### Information You Provide to Us

  * **Personal Information:** We access personal information provided by you, such as information provided at the time of (i) registration or in relation to use or modification of your account, (ii) request for on-demand services, customer support, or (iii) which is otherwise communicated to us which may include your name, gender, email address(es), mobile/phone number, mailing address(es), graduation year, graduation percentile, to (a) resolve any complaints/feedback in relation to the use of the Website, (b) enhance your experience of the Website; and (c) provide you with customized content/services on the Website.
  * **Sensitive Information:** We access your credit/debit card details (e.g. credit card number and related verification information), and other financial information such as bank account details, as well as related personal information, such as your name, address, mobile number, date of birth, education, professional experience, etc., at the time of making payments to the service providers through the approved payment processing provider for the services/products purchased through the Website.

### Information we collect through your use of the Website and/or the Services

  * **Usage and Preference Information:** We may access information about your interactions with the Website such as the date and time you use the Website, the areas or pages of the Website or internet resources that you visit (through the Website), the amount of time you spend viewing pages, the searches you make, the services you avail; and the settings you have chosen. The Website uses cookies, open device identifier number, web beacons or similar technologies to collect the information under this category. The Website Provider may use the above mentioned technologies to: (i) monitor the Website usage; and (ii) improve the content and services provided on and through the Website.
  * **Log Information:** When you interact with the Website, we collect server logs, which may include information like IP address, access dates and times, and other system activity, type of browser, and the third-party site or service you were using before interacting with the Website to understand the usage of the Website and the demographic information about the user base of the Website.
  * **Interactive Features/Forums Information:** The Website Provider will store any information you share using the interactive features (such as learning management system, online chat, online classroom sessions and email features) of the Website. You understand that any information (including personal information) which you may share through the interactive features with any third parties or other users of the Website will be solely at your risk as to the security of such information and the Website Provider cannot guarantee the security of such information or the nature of its use by the third parties to whom you disclose such information.
  * **Transaction Information:** We may access transaction details related to your use of the Website including the type of services requested, date and time of the request, complaints against the services sourced and other related transaction details to (i) monitor the Website usage; and (ii) improve the content and services provided on and through the Website.

_Cookies._ The Website Provider uses cookies, open device identifier number, web beacons or similar technologies to collect the information described above. A cookie is a small text file that may be stored on the hard drive of your device when you use the Website. The Website Provider may also use the above mentioned technologies to: (i) monitor the Website usage; and (ii) conduct research to improve the content and services provided on the Website.

The Website Provider also allows other companies such as web analytics partners to set or access their cookies or web beacons or similar technologies on the Website. For example, the Website Provider may use third party web analytics partners to analyze big-data on its behalf. These third-party analytics partners employ cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies to measure and analyze the big-data. To do so, these partners may use information about your use of the Website, which information will be anonymized such that it cannot reasonably be used to identify you. This data can also be used for online marketing purposes by the Website Provider.

### Collection Purposes, Use of Data

The Website Provider uses the data that is collected for the following general purposes:

  * To deliver the services made available through the Website
  * To respond to the request that you sent us such as your request for information, or your request to subscribe to a service;
  * To administer, protect and improve the Website;
  * To facilitate payments through the Website;
  * To better understand the preferences of users of the Website;
  * To identify server problems;
  * To compile aggregated statistics about usage of the Website;
  * To help personalize your experience of the Website;
  * To improve the services offered to you;
  * To help the Website Provider in its internal business functioning;
  * To provide you with information about technologies, product or service releases, news, and other communications;
  * To the extent permitted by applicable law, the Website Provider may combine various types of data that is collected; and
  * Any other use the Website Provider may describe at the point when it collects data.

### External Links on Website 

The Website may contain hyperlinks to other websites, content or resources. We have no control over any websites or resources, which are provided by other companies or persons. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such websites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that we are not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such websites or resources. These third-party service providers and third-party sites may have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your Personal information that you may be subject to. We recommend that when you enter a third-party website, you review the third-party site’s privacy policy as it relates to safeguarding your personal information. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the website. You may visit the third-party websites and choose to opt-out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising if the third party offers such an option. 

### Disclosures of Personal & Other Information

The Website Provider may share or transfer information you disclose on or is collected through the Website only for the following purposes: (i) to the approved payment processing provider(s), to facilitate the provision of Services through the Website; and(ii) as required by law or in the interest of protecting or exercising the Website Provider’s or others' legal rights, e.g., without limitation, in connection with requests from law enforcement officials and in connection with court proceedings. Your acceptance to this Policy or terms and conditions of this Website and/or usage of the Website shall be deemed to be your express consent to the Website Provider for sharing or disclosing any of your information or data (as mentioned herein) for the purpose and manner as provided in this Policy and no separate consent for any purpose shall be required.

### Access

If personal information you have submitted through the Website is no longer accurate, current, or complete, you are allowed to update these changes using the Website, but the Website Provider reserves the right to use information obtained previously to verify your identity or take other actions that it believes is appropriate.

### Confidentiality

You further acknowledge that the Website may contain information which is designated confidential by us and that you shall not disclose such information without our prior written consent. Your information is regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities or as per this Policy. We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail other than as per the terms of this Policy or our terms of service. 

### Website Communication

We have a strict ‘No Spam’ policy. We don’t share email address of our users for marketing purpose. We may send you certain emails in relation to the proper functioning of your account, your opinion of current services or of potential new services to be offered on the Website or any promotional material. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to customercare@talentsprint.com.

### Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active. Provided however, we may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or if required by law. 

### Security

The security of your personal information is a top priority for us. We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. Experts design our security measures and we use a variety of technologies and procedures to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Although the Website Provider takes reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, however, “perfect security”; does not exist on the Internet. You therefore agree that any security breaches beyond the control of our standard security procedures are at your sole risk and discretion. Your use of Website is subjected to our Policy and Terms of Service. If you do not agree to this we request you not to use this portal

### Amendments

The Website Provider reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time, but will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the Policy the date it was last updated. When you use the Website, you are accepting the current version of this Policy as posted on the Website at that time. It is recommended that users revisit this Policy on occasion to learn of any changes.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions, or concerns about this Policy or any complaints or grievances about the manner in which the Website Provider handles your personal information or the use of your personal information (in doing so acknowledging that the Website Provider may be unable to provide you all or some of the services), please feel free to contact the Grievance Officer any time at 

Contact Details: **customercare@talentsprint.com**

**[Note: You acknowledge and agree that you will have to send an email to customercare@talentsprint.com if you wish to delete/disable your account and have all your information deleted from the Website databases and servers.]**

THE USE OF THE WEBSITE OR ANY PART OF THE SERVICES ON THE WEBSITE, EITHER IN WHOLE OR IN PART, SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

Last Updated: July 25, 2019
